William E. L. Bunn
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Material, 1896-2009, Series 8:; (Box 7-8, 12, OV 21; 1.4 linear feet)
  - Simplified Scientific Ephemeris, circa 1940s-1959, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
  - Theater Programs, circa 1932-1936, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, circa 1930s-2004 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Oversize Magazines, 1988, 1990, (Oversized items from box 8, folder 3) (Box 12)
  - Posters, circa 1980s, (Oversized items items from box 8, folder 8) (Box OV 21, Folder 8)
- Photographs, 1863-1990s, Series 9:; (Box 8-9, 13; 1.6 linear feet)
  Personal photographs include snapshots and portraits of Bunn, photographs of his wife, Annavene, and children, Cheri and Eric. Also found are numerous photographs of family and friends, including two family photograph albums. Many of these photographs are unidentified. Photographs also depict artwork by Bunn, however, researchers should note that additional photographs of artwork are included among the project files in Series 3. Additional photographs depict various subjects that were of interest to Bunn and may have been used as references for his artwork, including nature scenes, steamboats, airplanes, and bridges.
  - William Bunn, 1929-1990s, (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 20-23)
  - Annavene Bunn, circa 1930s-1940s, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 24-25)
  - Family, circa 1900-1960s, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 26-28)
  - Family and Friends, circa 1930s-1990s, (7 folders) (Box 8, Folder 29-35)
  - Chari Bunn Petrowski Dance Recitals, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 50th Wedding Anniversary, circa 1989, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - Hawaii Vacation, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - Vacation, circa 1950s (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Family Photograph Album, 1863-early 1900s (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Family Photograph Album, 1920s-1930s, (Oversized item housed in box 13) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Loose Page from Photograph Album, circa 1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Photographs for Torso Project, 1930s (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Artwork, 1930s-1990s, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 11-13)
  - Airplanes and Gliders, circa 1948-1970s (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Bridges, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Houses, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Landscapes and Nature, 1950s-1980s, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
  - Medal Designs, circa 1963 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Neo-classical Iowa City House, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - River Scenery, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Steamboats, circa 1930s-1950s, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 22-24)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, circa 1930s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Lithograph Printing Plates, circa 1950s (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Slides, circa 1962-1989 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Oversize Family Photograph Album, 1920s-1930s, (Oversized item from box 9, folder 8) (Box 13)
- Artwork, circa 1926-2004, Series 10:; (Box 9-11, 14, OVs 22-30, RD 32; 2.3 linear feet)
  Artwork primarily consists of pencil drawings, watercolors, and pastels. Found here are costume and theater designs created as part of William Bunn's thesis at University of Iowa. Also included are drawings and watercolors for potential art projects. Researchers should note that many of the miscellaneous drawings here were most likely preliminary drawings and studies for works documented in Series 3: Project Files or technical drawings from his work as an industrial designer. Drawings frequently depict steamboats, airplanes, people, and mechanical designs. Additionally, there are four sketchbooks. Two of these sketchbooks contain sketches and notes for the post office murals in Minden, Nebraska, and Hamburg, Iowa.
  - Artwork by Others, circa 1933, (Oversized items housed in box 14) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Christmas Card Design, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Costume Designs, circa 1933-1934, (3 folders; oversized items housed in box 14) (Box 9, Folder 30-32)
  - Drawings for "Classroom Teaching," circa 1955 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Drawings for "Deva Officiating in the Blue Temple," 1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Drawings for "Deva Officiating in the Crimson Temple," circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Drawings for "Education Forming Mental Images," circa 1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Drawings for "First Meeting at Colony," circa 1955 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Drawings for "View of the Grounds," circa 1955 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Drawings of Automobiles, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Drawings of Steamboats, circa 1940s-1960s, (Oversized items housed in OV 22) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Drawings, "New Paintings Project Ideas," circa 1940s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Drawings, "Potential Art Projects," circa 1940s-1970s, (5 folders) (Box 10, Folder 10-14)
  - Drawings, Miscellaneous, circa 1928-1980s, (3 folders; oversized items housed in box 14, OVs 23-27, and RD 32) (Box 10, Folder 15-17)
  - Figure Drawings, circa 1930s, (Oversized items housed in box 14) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - House Plans, circa 1979, (Oversized items housed in box 14) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Painting of Airplane, circa 1940s (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Painting of Swimming Pool, circa 1940s (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Painting of War Scene, circa 1940s, (Oversized item housed in OV 28) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Painting of a Woman, circa 1940s (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Paintings of Portaits on Board, circa 1940s (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Paintings, Miscellaneous, circa 1930s-1960s, (Oversized items housed in OVs 29-30) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Pastel Portraits, circa 1930s, (Oversized items housed in box 14) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Puppet Sketchbook, circa 1931-1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - School Artwork, circa 1926-1933, (Oversized items housed in box 14) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Sketchbook, Library Triptych Mural, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sketchbook #4, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sketchbook #5, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Studies on Anatomy, circa 1940s (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Theater Designs, circa 1930s, (Oversized items housed in box 14) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Thesis, "A Project in Stage Design for an Early Eighteenth Century Play "The Mourning Bride" of William Congreve," 1936 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Thesis Tracings and Drawings, 1936, (3 folders) (Box 11, Folder 8-10)
  - Watercolor by Cheri Bunn, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Oversize Artwork by Others, circa 1933, (Oversized items from box 9, folder 28) (Box 14)
  - Oversize Costume Designs, circa 1933-1934, (Oversized items from box 9, folder 32) (Box 14)
  - Oversize Drawings, Miscellaneous, circa 1928-1980s, (Oversized items from box 10, folder 17) (Box 14)
  - Oversize Figure Drawings, circa 1930s, (Oversized items from box 10, folder 18) (Box 14)
  - Oversize House Plans, circa 1979, (Oversized items from box 10, folder 19) (Box 14)
  - Oversize Pastel Portraits, circa 1930s, (Oversized items from box 10, folder 26) (Box 14)
  - Oversize School Artwork, circa 1926-1933, (Oversized items from box 11, folder 1) (Box 14)
  - Oversize Theater Designs, circa 1930s, (Oversized items from box 11, folder 6) (Box 14)
  - Oversize Drawings of Steamboats, circa 1940s-1960s, (Oversized items from box 10, folder 8) (Box OV 22)
  - Oversize Drawings, Miscellaneous, circa 1928-1980s, (Oversized items from box 10, folder 17) (Box OV 23-27)
  - Oversize Painting of War Scene, circa 1940s, (Oversized item from box 10, folder 22) (Box OV 28)
  - Oversize Paintings, Miscellaneous, circa 1930s-1960s, (Oversized item from box 10, folder 25) (Box OV 29-30)
  - Oversize Drawings, Miscellaneous, circa 1928-1980s, (Oversized items from box 10, folder 17) (Box RD 32)